{
    "email": "hola@agiletesting.la",
    "country": "PE",
    "company": "Interbank Canales",
    "industry": "banca",
    "answers":[
        {"question":"SprintNoEsUnaCascada","answer":2.5},
        {"question":"TresAmigos","answer":3.5},
        {"question":"ParticiparDesdeElInicio","answer":3.5},
        {"question":"TodosHacenTesting","answer":2.5},
        {"question":"TodosSonResponsables","answer":3},
        {"question":"PiramidePruebas","answer":2},
        {"question":"NoSeNecesitaTareasManuales","answer":3},
        {"question":"EjecutanContinuamente","answer":2},
        {"question":"ResultadosTransparentes","answer":3},
        {"question":"RiskBasedTesting","answer":2},
        {"question":"ExploratoryTesting","answer":2.5},
        {"question":"DisenoPruebaIterativo","answer":3},
        {"question":"BalancePruebas","answer":2},
        {"question":"EstandaresConsistentes","answer":3},
        {"question":"FeedbackEsPorMejoras","answer":4}        
    ]
}